天呐
Oh, man!
-怎么回事  -崔格在通洗澡间的下水道
- What's that? - Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
这是什么鬼东西
What in the name of hell?
可能是你的人字拖
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
这是A片吗
Is this porn?
怎么了  我一定是按到什么了
What I'm doing? I must have hit something on the remote.
我们有付钱吗
Do we pay for this?
不  我们连有线电视费都没给
No! We didn't even pay our cable bill.
也许这是他们的处罚方式
Maybe this is how they punish us.
也许我们应该欠电话费  免费色情电话哦
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill. Free phone sex.
也许我们应该欠煤气费
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
看啊  那位小姐没穿衣服
Hey, that lady's all kinds of naked.
乔伊不知道按了什么  它就冒了出来
Joey just pressed something on the remote and it just came on.
我有一次也按到过  突然就出来了
Yeah, it happened to me once. I was just flipping through the channels and bam!
跟检到钱一样爽
It was like finding money.
还是印有春宫图的钱
Like finding money with naked people on it!
但我错手把电视关掉了
But I made the mistake of turning off the TV.
之后就再也找不到了
I never got it back again.
我好伤心
And I'm sad.
他干嘛要关电视
Why would he turn off the TV?
拜托  吃饭的时候一定要看这个吗
All right, you know what, come on, do we really have to watch this while we eat?
我们不知道  哪种行为会让它消失
We don't know what could make this go away.
所以谁都不许碰遥控器  也不许碰电视
So no one touches the remote, and no one touches the TV..
连电视周围的空气都不能扰动
And no one touches the air around the TV.
就像有一个A片保护罩
Imagine a protective porn bubble, if you will.
起码也要静音
I'm at least going to mute it.
A片还在
We still have porn.
你干什么  那个很重的  给我
What are you doing? That's too heavy. Give it here.
哦  天呐
Oh, God.
我怀孕了  再也没法扛着按摩桌到处跑了
I'm too pregnant for this, lugging around a stupid massage table.
我得找个桌子小一点的工作
I need a job with a smaller table.
或是不需要桌子的工作
Or a job without a carry table
你的意思是  比如医生
You mean, like a doctor?
菲比  你挡到A片了
Pheebe, you're blocking the porn! Come om!
这让我想起今天我还要做产检
That reminds me. I have to see my ob-gyn today.
艾蜜莉去机场了
Emily just went to the airport.
你怎么不去送送她
Why didn't you take her?
她叔叔早就讲好要送她了
Her uncle had already planned to do it.
我们今天早上告过别了
We said our goodbyes this morning.
你一定很难受
You must feel horrible.
对了  隔壁有免费的A片
Hey, the guys have free porn.
高兴一点  你们会再见面的
Hey, cheer up. You gonna see her again, right?
就因为我不知道
That's the thing. I don't know.
每当我提起  她就说
When I brought it up her, she said. . .
这样就很棒了  何必谈到未来
"This is so fantastic. Why talk about the future?
-我们就享受...  -别学英国腔
- Let's enjoy...  - Don't do the accent.
你会再见到她的
You've got to see her again.
-你为什么这么在意  -因为我...
- Why do you care so much? - Because...
因为你可以实现我的幻想
You could get to live out my fantasy.
你对艾蜜莉有幻想
You had fantasies about Emily?
你懂得  就是那个幻想嘛
You know, the fantasy.
认识个异乡人  疯狂坠入爱河  然后共度一生
Meet someone from a foreigner land, fall madly in love and spend your lives together.
所以你上学的时候  老跟那个乌克兰男生鬼混
Is that why you junior high, you hung out with that Ukrainian kid?
还有  他妈妈煮什么菜都要加酸奶油
Yeah, plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything.
你爱她吗
Do you love her?
我们说好只在一起二个星期
We said it would only be two weeks you know.
可你爱她
You love her.
说真的  什么是爱
What is love, really?
我就知道你爱她
I knew you loved her!
你得去机场告诉她
You go to the airport and tell her.
你应该能在登机门前追上她
You'll probably catch her just when she's front go to the gate.
你呼喊她的名字  并大喊"我爱你"
You'll call her name and yell "I love you! "
然后她会说"我也爱你"
She'll say "I love you too! "
然后你们会有最深情的一吻
Then you will have the most amazing kiss.
登机门前掌声如雷
Everyone at the gate will applaud.
我可是接吻高手哦
I am a good kisser.
然后你们可以溜进驾驶舱
Then you two can sneak into the cockpit.
气氛开始变得火热
Things will start to heat up.
然后一个空姐进来...
And then a stewardess comes in...
我最近A片看多了
I've been watching too much porn.
-那是心跳吗  -没错
- Is that the heartbeat? - That's it.
哦  天呐
Oh, my God!
太酷了
This is so cool!
我们谈过多胞胎的可能性吗
Have we talked about the possibility of multiple births?
先搞定这一胎再说吧
Let's take care of this one.
要是再怀孕  我有你的名片
If I get pregnant again, I have your card.
不是  我听到三个相互独立的心跳音
No, I'm getting three separate heartbeats.
三个  不是说我连一胎都怀不上吗
Three. You guys were worried I wouldn't even have one.
医生经常犯错的
Doctors are wrong all the time
你确定有三个
Are you sure that there are three?
-绝对没错  -天呐  天呐  -天呐
- Definitely. - Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
再过几个月  我的体内
So in a few months, I'll have
是不是会有三个宝宝逛大街
three babies walking around inside me?
然后会像激流涌进的木船一样冲出来
It'll be like one of those log rides when they come shooting out.
其实生三个跟生一个一样
Giving birth to three is not that different from giving birth to one.
你懂什么
What do you know?
产检结果怎样
How'd it go at the doctor's?
你知道的啦  当你走在街上
You know how, when you're walking down the street. . .
看到三个人走成一列
and you see three people in a row.
你肯定会说"哦  真好"
And you say "Oh, that's nice. "
-懂了  -懂了就好
-Yes. - Ok.
好消息  你将有三个宝宝
Good news! You'll have three babies.
三个宝宝
Three babies?
我总算可以组乐团了
I've finally got my band!
我们会是个大家庭  我一直想要大家庭
We'll have a big family! I always wanted a big family.
哦  老天  你们高兴就好
Oh, God, I'm so glad you're happy!
我还怕你们会抓狂呢
I was afraid you'd be freaked.
为什么要抓狂
Why would we be freaked?
因为三个养起来更累  也更花钱
Because it's harder to raise them and the added expense.
也对
That's right.
不  高兴些呀  高兴些呀
No, back to happy. Back to happy!
没没没  没问题的...
No, No, No. It's going to be fine. . .
因为我教家政
because I teach home ec.
所以  我可以让30个学生
I can have 30 kids
一整年都做婴儿服
making baby clothes all year long.
就像我专属的廉价童装厂
It'll be like my very own little sweatshop.
自从你说是三胞胎  我就在想
I was thinking, ever since you said we'd have triplets.
我最好休学去找一份工作
The best thing for me to do is drop out of college and get a job.
-不  法兰克  -你不能放弃学业
- No, Frank. - No! You can't quit college.
你在念书
You're in college?
冷冻库专校
Refrigerator college.
当我们发现你有了孩子...
When we found out we were having a baby...
我就在想  我应该有份事业
I figured I should have a career, you know?
而且我也很喜欢冷冻库
And I love refrigerators.
你不能放弃你的梦想
You can't give up on your dream!
没关系  我们家将有三个孩子
No, it's okay. We're going to have three kids.
那是个不一样的梦
And that's a different kind of dream.
三个孩子  然后一贫如洗
Three kids and no money.
搭乘009班机的旅客请登机
This is the boarding call for flight 009.
-艾蜜莉  -你怎么在这里
- Emily. - What are you doing here?
我得在你走之前  再见你一面
I had to see you before you took off.
你真好
You are so sweet.
好大的巧克力棒
That's a big candy bar.
我跟你在一起  过得好开心
I had the most amazing time with you.
我也是
Me too.
009班机起飞前最后一次通知
This is the final boarding call for flight 009.
那是我的班机
Well, that's me.
给你
Here, have this.
只能有一件登机行李
I'm only allowed one piece of carry-on.
等一下  我有事要告诉你
Listen, I have to tell you something.
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
我就直说了
I'm just going to say it, okay?
我觉得
I think...
我爱你
I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
It's no problem.
这到底是什么歌  我一整天都在哼
What is that song that's be in my head all day?
《善意做爱》的主题曲
It's the theme from Good Will Humping.
你们知道有谁不喜欢A片吗
You know who doesn't even like dirty movies?
我的新男友约书亚
My boyfriend Joshua.
是啊
Yeah, right.
他说他喜欢保留一点想像的空间
He said he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.
他有没有说那些对白很低俗
Did he also say that the dialogue was corny?
非常可笑  一点都不性感
And that he found it funny, not sexy?
没错
Yes.
他喜欢A片
Yeah, he likes porn.
你去哪里
Where you going?
去看看他是不是真的觉得  超级名模都太瘦
To find out if he really thinks models are too skinny.
他们反应如何
How'd it go?
法兰克想休学...
Frank has to quit college...
因为他很能生的姐姐一次怀了三胎
because his super-fertile sister's having three babies.
我得赶快赚钱  我有个想法想跟你谈谈
I need to make money fast. I had an idea I wanted to talk to you about.
因为你在大公司上班
You work for a big company.
内线交易
Insider trading.
你有什么内幕可以给我
What information can you give me?
头儿不会跟我们讲这些
They don't talk to us about that stuff.
但我可以给你免费的立可白
But I can get you free White-Out.
-你有照我说的告诉她吗  -有
- Did you do what I said? Did you tell her? - I did.
她怎么说
What'd she say?
谢谢
"Thank you. "
不客气  她说什么了
You're totally welcome. What'd she say?
她说  "谢谢"
She said, "Thank you. "
我说"我爱你"
I said, "I love you. "
而她却说  "谢谢"
And she said, "Thank you. "
你说你爱她了
Did you say you love her?
你想让她怎么做
What were you trying to get her to do?
现在怎么办
What do I do?
你得欲擒故纵
You play hard-to-get.
她住在伦敦
She already lives in London.
那你就去东京
So you go to Tokyo.
算了
Forget it. Forget it.
你说了"我爱你"  这事完了
You told her you love her. It's over.
谁说的  你们才完了呐
It is not over! You're over!
什么
What?
你自己明白
You know.
好吧  说得好
Ok. Good one.
事情还没完  她会打电话来  说她爱你
It's not over. She'll call and tell you she loves you.
她先前不说  是因为
And the reason why she couldn't, is because
她的感觉强烈到令她害怕
her feelings were so strong, it scared her.
快回去等电话  她可能会从飞机上打
Go home and wait for her call. She could call from the plane.
要是她没打来  那就是完了
But if she doesn't call, it is definitely over!
不对  如果最后我打给她  问她发生了什么
Unless, eventually, I call her to see what's going on...
然后她说  她会再打给我  结果没打
and she says she'll call me back, but then she doesn't.
那才是真的完了
Then it's over!
真够坚强的  汉子
Way to be strong, man!
我们可以看卡通吗
Can we watch cartoons on your TV?
我们需要休息一下
We need a porn break.
我们看了两小时的"杀进杀出又杀进"了
We spent two hours watching In and Out and In Again.
关掉不就得了
Why don't you turn it off?
那我们会变成关掉免费A片的白痴
Then we'd be the guys who turned off free porn.
太好了  你们都在
Good, you're here!
你手上拿的什么
What you got there?
这个  问得好
This? I'm glad you asked.
你不是讨厌用普通刀子切易拉罐吗
Don't you hate to cut a tin can with an ordinary steak knife?
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
孕妇发狂砍杀四人
Pregnant woman slays four?
-你没买下这些刀子吧  -没有
- Did they make you pay for those knives? - No.
-你确定  -我确定
- Are you sure? - No.
卖刀赚不了多少钱帮弗兰克的
You won't make enough money that can help Frank out just by selling knives.
可是我需要后续计划的本钱
I know that. I just need enough money for the second part of my plan.
后续计划是什么
What's the second part of your plan?
经销土星轿车
My Saturn dealership.
旅途还顺利吗
How was your flight?
很糟糕
It was dreadful.
你对我深情告白  我却反应那么差劲
It was terrible how I acted when you said those wonderful things.
没关系
No, that's all right.
我很高兴你打来
I'm just glad you called.
罗斯  我有事要告诉你
Ross, there's something that I've got to tell you.
我有男朋友的
There's someone else.
这句话在英国的意思  跟在美国一样吗
Does that mean the same thing in England as it does in America?
她不知道她想要谁  我还是那个叫柯林的
She doesn't know who she wants. Me or this "Colin" guy.
本来就应该这样  第三者休想插足
This isn't how it's supposed to go. There can't be another guy.
对了  当然得有第三者啦
Of course, there's another guy!
这样更完美
This is even more perfect.
现在你得证明你的爱
You have to prove your love!
我什么也不证明  我再也不会听你的了
I'm not proving anything. I'm done listening to you.
要不是被你说服跑去机场
If I hadn't let you talk me into the airport in the first place,
我也不会搞到去捶墙
I wouldn't have put my fist through the wall.
你捶墙了
You put your fist through the wall?
没锤着墙  锤着门了
I missed and hit the door.
不过门弹得很有力
But it opened really hard.
你得去伦敦  你得为了她去一趟伦敦
You have to go to London. You have to go fight for her.
有道理
That makes sense.
你说你爱她  她没有回应
You already said you loved her, and she didn't say it back.
然后她打电话来  说他有男朋友
Then she told you about another guy.
去伦敦吧  她会被你吓死的
Go to London. Scare her!
瑞秋跟保罗在一起时  你都做了什么
When Rachel was with Paolo, what did you do?
我嘲笑他的口音
I made fun of his accent.
你让他轻松得手  你完全没争取  没错吧
You sat back and let him have her. You didn't fight. Right?
-你想让艾蜜莉也被抢走 -不想
- You want the same thing that to happen with Emily? - No.
好  那就去争取她
All right then, go fight for her!
去伦敦
Go to London!
你和艾蜜莉也可以那样
That could be you and Emily.
比他们要唯美些
That but nicer.
去伦敦吧
Just go to London!
当真要去
Really?
快点  给她个惊喜
Come on. Surprise her.
别把她拱手让人
Don't let her go without a fight.
好吧  好吧  就这么决定了
All right. All right. I'm going to do it.
我要去伦敦争取她
I'm going to London, and I'll fight for her.
好  加油
Okay. Good luck!
罗斯  你到了机场能不能帮我买
Ross if you get to the airport can you pick me up
特大三角巧克力
one of those Toblerone bars
我想到了  我想到赚钱的路子了
I did it! I figured out a way to make money.
我要开按摩院  法兰克会来帮我
I'll open a massage place. Frank will help me.
按他课程表营业  他就不用退学了
We'll work it around his schedule, so he doesn't have to quit school.
听起来很好  但你的本钱从哪里来呢
That’s sounds great, but how are you going to afford it?
我们走在街上  看见那辆
We were walking down the street,
你们用来办外烩的货车
and we saw your van.
-于是我们就想到  -我来说  我来说
- And we realized-- - I'm telling it! I'm telling it!
人们通勤的时候  也需要按摩放松
People need transportation, and they need massages to relax.
我们可以把两者结合起来
We can combine the two.
我按摩  法兰克开车
I give massages and Frank drives.
我可以在货车里装个桌子
I'll bolt a table in the van,
你们明白了没
and you know what I've got?
有进无出的死亡货车
A place that no one will get out of alive?
不是  你们想啊  其实就是
No. Think about it. It's a taxi that
给想放松的人搭的计程车
people take when they need to relax.
叫"轻松任你行"
It's a Relaxi-Taxi!
我最想讲的就是名字
The name was my favorite part!
名字是我想出来的
I came up with it.
你乱讲
You did not!
你想的"轻松之行"  一点也不好
You came up with Relaxi-Cab. That's not good.
天呐  你在英国啦  艾蜜莉惊喜不
Oh, my god! Ross are you in England? Was Emily surprised?
没有  因为她还没回家
No, she hasn't come home yet.
她整晚都没回家  显然是跟那个人在一起
She hasn't been home all night. She must be with the other guy.
我就是个蹲在这里守夜的白痴
I'm the stupid moron who spent the night here.
下一班飞机是几点
When is the next flight out?
大约4小时后
About four hours.
再等一下  如果她还不出现  再回来
Stay there for a couple of hours. If she doesn't show up, come home.
告诉他"轻松任你行"的事
Tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
问他是不是比"轻松之行"好
Ask him if he likes it better than Relaxi-Cab.
不是"轻松之行"  是"轻松车行"
It's not Relaxi-Cab. It's Relaxi-Cab.
就像"计程车行"一样
Like Taxi-Cab.
哦  这个更好
Oh. That is better.
我们是在伦敦吗
Are we in London?
你怎么在这里  你不能在这里
Why are you doing here? You can't be here.
我有话要对罗斯说
I've come to talk to Ross.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing.
我本来想打给他的...
I was going to call him--
你是来说你爱他的  我就知道
You came to tell him you love him. I knew it!
我是对的  我是对的吧
I was right! I'm right, right?
我只是想跟他谈谈
I'd rather talk to him.
我去过他家  可他不在
I've been to his apartment and he's not there.
我得跟他谈谈 你们知道他在哪里吗
I need to talk to him. Do you have any idea where he is?
罗斯  你在吗
Ross, are you there?
不知道你能不能听到  但我还是得说
Ross, I don't know if you hear this, but I'll talk anyway.
我在美国  跟你妹妹和朋友们在一起
I'm in the States with your sister and friends.
我跟柯林分手了
It's all over with Colin.
我来这就是想告诉你这件事  还有...
I came here to tell you that and to tell you--
乔伊  你想要巧克力尽管拿
Yes, Joey, you can have all the chocolate you want. Just take it.
我是来告诉你  我爱你
I came here to tell you that I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too!
我现在就去电话亭  打电话给你
I'll call you right now from the phone booth.
现在你听不到我
You can't hear me.
真想知道  你听不听得见
I wish I knew if you'd heard me.
我想我刚才要么是在向你表白
I suppose I've either just told you I love you
要么就是让邻居看了笑话
or given my neighbours a good laugh.
纽曼太太  如果你在听
Mrs. Newman, if you're listening,
快滚开  这不关你的事
bugger off. None of your business.
我想  你八成听不见
I suppose there's not much chance you did hear that.
而且有电话进来了
There's the call waiting...
我得挂了  就这样吧
so I should go. Well.
罗斯  我爱你
Ross, I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我刚才去银行  那里有个很火辣的出纳
I was just at the bank. There was this really hot teller.
但她并没有领我去金库嘿咻嘿咻
and she didn't ask me to do it with her in the vault.
我也是
Same kind thing happened to me.
披萨外送小妹放下披萨  收了钱就走了
Pizza delivery girl comes over, gives me the pizza takes the money and leaves!
没说"你家好漂亮"  "卧房一定很大吧"
No "Nice apartment, bet the bedrooms are huge"?
完全没有
No! Nothing!
你知道吗  我们得把A片关掉
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.
你说得对
I think you're right.
准备好了吗
Ready?
一  二  三
One, two, three.
感觉不错
That's kind of nice.
有种解脱感
That's kind of a relief.
-想不想看看它还在不在  -当然
- You want to see if we still have it? - Yeah.
-免费A片  -我们有免费A片啦
- Free porn! - We have free porn!